Guide to the Joshua A. Fishman Papers
Department of Special Collections
Joshua A. Fishman papers
1885-1992
1926-1992
M0695
Fishman, Joshua A.
ca. 200 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
The Joshua A. Fishman papers include correspondence; writings by Fishman (both published and unpublished); lecture notes and transcripts; audio and video tapes of some of Fishman's lectures; course outlines and notes representing most of the institutions where he taught; reviews of Fishman's books; interviews; documents relating to Fishman's work at several centers for advanced study; tributes honoring Fishman; language cartoons; research materials used in producing five of his books; and other research materials largely pertaining to language and ethnicity. Several series in this collection are bilingual (in English and Yiddish). Fishman's correspondence is multilingual, including documents in English, Yiddish, Hebrew, Spanish, French, German, Russian, and Basque. Included in the collection are card file indexes to his correspondence and his written work.
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dr. Fishman, 1993 (Accn 1993-145; and 2011 (Accn MSS.2011-023).
Biography / Administrative History
Dr. Joshua Aaron Fishman is a renowned social scientist and a founder of the field of sociolinguistics. An acclaimed researcher, Dr. Fishman's interests include language and ethnicity, language spread and change, Yiddish studies, bilingual education, and traditional folk medicine. In the course of his career, Dr. Fishman has accumulated multiple honors and awards. He has been a visiting fellow at almost all of the major Centers for Advanced Study in the world and has published more than 800 scholarly articles and books in both Yiddish and English. Dr. Fishman was born on July 18, 1926, in Philadelphia to Aaron Samuel Fishman and Sonia (Horwitz) Fishman. He earned his B.S. and M.S. in social studies from the University of Pennsylvania in 1948 and his Ph.D. in social psychology from Columbia University in 1953. On December 23, 1951, he married Gella Schweid, with whom he has three children: M. Manuel, David Eliot, and Avrom. After his graduation from Columbia, Fishman worked for some years as an educational researcher, first for the Jewish Education Committee of New York and then for the College Entrance Examination Board in New York City. He also was on the faculty of the psychology department of The City College of the City University of New York (then City College) from 1955-1958. Subsequently, he worked as an associate professor and as Director of Research at the Albert M. Greenfield Center for Human Relations at the University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, until 1960. In 1960 he was hired by Yeshiva University, where he has remained on the faculty until the present day; he became an emeritus professor in 1988. He began spending parts of the academic year at Stanford University in 1963, and in 1992 was designated a visiting professor of linguistics at Stanford. Dr. Fishman also has held summer or visiting appointments at Indiana University, Hebrew University (Jerusalem), Philippine Normal College (Manila), Harvard University, Columbia University, the University of Hawaii, the University of Illinois, the University of San Francisco, and the University of New Mexico. The positions and titles that Dr. Fishman holds as of 2006: - Distinguished University Research Professor of Social Sciences, Emeritus (Ferkauf Graduate School of Psychology), Yeshiva University. - Visiting Professor and Visiting Scholar, School of Education, Applied Linguistics and Department of Linguistics, Stanford University. - Adjunct Professor of Multilingual and Multicultural Education, School of Education, New York University. - Visiting Professor of Linguistics, City University of New York, Graduate Center
Scope and Content of Collection
The Joshua A. Fishman papers contain documents dating from 1885 to the 1990s (the bulk of the collection dates from 1926-1992). The collection include correspondence; writings by Fishman (both published and unpublished); lecture notes and transcripts; audio and video tapes of some of Fishman?s lectures; course outlines and notes; reviews of Fishman?s books; interviews; documents relating to Fishman?s work at several centers for advanced study; tributes honoring Fishman; recommendations and evaluations by Fishman [not open to research use]; language cartoons; and research materials. Several series in this collection are bilingual (in English and Yiddish). Fishman?s correspondence is multilingual, including documents in English, Yiddish, Hebrew, Spanish, French, German, Russian, and Basque.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Fishman, Joshua A.; Fishman, Gella Schweid.; Bilingualism.; Ethnicity.; Language and languages--Political aspects.; Linguistic minorities.; Linguistics.; Sociolinguistics.; Yiddish language.; Yiddish literature.; Yiddish poetry.; Jewish studies.; Yiddish secular schools.
Arrangement
Organized into 17 series: Correspondence 1926-1992; 2. Published and unpublished works 1940s-1990s; 3. Lectures and talks given ca. 1940-1992; 4. Course outlines and notes 1940-1993; 5. Book Reviews, Prefaces and Forwards 1950s-1990s; 6. Interviews 1965-1991; 7. Publicity/Travel Arrangements 1947-1992; 8. Centers for Advanced Studies 1963-83; 9. Tributes and Celebrations Honoring JAF 1986-1991; 10. JAF Notes on Work of Colleagues; 11. Recommendations 1960s-1990s [Access to this series is restricted.]; 12. Academic Institutions with Fishman Affiliation 1940s-1990s; 13. Royalty Statements to JAF 1968-1991; 14. Research Topics and Materials; 15. Language cartoons collection; 16. Research materials in preparation for the writing of his books, 1885-1991; 17. Material received in 2011 (Accn MSS.2011-023).
Container List
- Series 1 Correspondence to and from J. A. Fishman and J.A. Fishman/G. S. Fishman, 1926-1992
  This series is multilingual, with documents in English, Yiddish, Hebrew, Spanish, French, German, Russian, and Basque. It includes joint correspondence to/from Dr. Fishman and his wife, memorabilia and documents pertaining to events or activities in which Dr. Fishman (and/or his wife) participated (see the "general file" for each year), and e-mails from Israel written in February/March of 1991 during the Gulf War SCUD missile attacks (box 109, folders 4-6). Boxes 117-133 contain a card-file index of the people to and from whom correspondence was sent. Organized by date
  - 1926 General (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1937 July (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1939 General (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1940 General (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1940 August/February/January (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1941 General (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1941 August/October (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1942 General (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1942 May/August/Sept/Nov (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1943 General (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1943 Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1943 May/August/July/Sep (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1944 General (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1944 June/May/April (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1945 General (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1945 August (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1946 General (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1946 Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1946 August/May/March (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1947 General (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1947 Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1947 December-March (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1948 General (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1948 Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1948 December-May (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1949 General (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1949 Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1949 December-June (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1949 May-January (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1950 General (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1950 Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1950 December-September (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1950 August-April (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1950 March-January (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1951 General (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1951 General (Cont'd. 1) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1951 General (Cont'd. 2) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1951 General (Cont'd. 3) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1951 General (Cont'd. 4) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1951 General (Cont'd. 5) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1951 Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1951 Undated-December (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1951 December (Cont/d.) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1951 November (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1951 October (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1951 September (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1951 August (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1951 July (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1951 June (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1951 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1951 April (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1951 March (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1951 February (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1951 January (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1952 General (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1952 Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1952 December (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1952 November (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1952 October (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1952 September (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1952 August (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1952 July (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1952 June (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1952 May (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1952 April (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1952 March (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1952 February (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1952 January (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1953 General (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1953 Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1953 December (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1953 November (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1953 October (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1953 September (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1953 August (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1953 July (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1953 June (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1953 May (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1953 April (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1953 March (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1953 March (Cont'd.) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1953 February (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1953 February (Cont'd.) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1953 January (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 1953 January (Cont'd.) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1954 General (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1954 Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1954 December (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1954 November (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1954 October (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1954 September (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1954 August (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1954 July (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1954 July (Cont'd.) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1954 June (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1954 May (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1954 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1954 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1954 April (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1954 March (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1954 February (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1954 January (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1955 General (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1955 Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1955 December (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1955 November (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1955 October (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1955 September (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1955 August (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1955 July (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1955 June (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1955 May (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1955 April (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1955 March (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1955 January (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 1956 November (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 1956 October (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1956 August (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1956 July (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1956 June (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1956 May (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 1956 April (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 1956 March (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1956 February (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 1956 January (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 1957 General (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 1957 November (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 1957 October (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - 1957 September (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - 1957 August (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 1957 July (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - 1957 June (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 1957 May (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - 1957 April (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 1957 March (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1957 March (Cont'd.) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1957 February (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1957 January (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1958 General (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1958 December (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1958 November (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1958 October (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1958 September (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1958 August (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1958 July (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1958 June (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1958 May (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1958 April (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1958 March (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1958 February (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1958 January (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 1958 January (Cont'd.) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1959 General (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1959 Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1959 December (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1959 November (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1959 October (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1959 September (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1959 August (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1959 July (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1959 June (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1959 May (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1959 April (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1959 March (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1959 February (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 1959 January (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1960 General (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1960 Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 1960 December (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 1960 November (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1960 October (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 1960 September (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 1960 August (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1960 July (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1960 June (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1960 May (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1960 April (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1960 March (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1960 February (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1960 January (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1961 General (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1961 December (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1961 November (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1961 October (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1961 September (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1961 August (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1961 August (Cont'd.) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1961 July (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1961 June (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1961 May (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1961 April (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1961 March (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1961 February (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 1961 January (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 1962 General (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1962 December (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1962 November (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1962 October (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1962 September (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1962 August (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 1962 July (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 1962 June (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 1962 May (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1962 April (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 1962 March (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1962 February (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1962 January (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1963 General (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1963 Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1963 December (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1963 November (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1963 October (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 1963 October (Cont'd.) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 1963 September (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1963 September (Cont'd.) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1963 August (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1963 July (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1963 June (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1963 May (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1963 April (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 1963 March (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1963 February (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1963 January (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 1964 General (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 1964 Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 1964 December (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 1964 November (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 1964 October (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 1964 September (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1964 August (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 1964 July (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1964 June (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 1964 May (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 1964 April (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 1964 April (Cont'd.) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 1964 March (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1964 March (Cont'd.) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 1964 February (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 1964 February (Cont'd.) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 1964 January (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 1964 January (Cont'd.) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1965 General (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 1965 December (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 1965 November (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 1965 November (Cont'd.) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1965 October (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1965 September (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 1965 August (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 1965 July (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 1965 June (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 1965 May (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 1965 April (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 1965 March (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 1965 February (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 1965 January (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - 1966 General (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1966 Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1966 December (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 1966 November (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1966 October (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1966 September (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 1966 August (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 1966 July (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1966 June (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1966 May (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1966 April (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 1966 March (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 1966 February (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1966 January (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1967 General (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 1967 Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 1967 December (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 1967 November (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 1967 October (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 1967 September (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 1967 August (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 1967 July (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 1967 June (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1967 May (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1967 April (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1967 March (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1967 February (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 1967 January (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 1968 General (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 1968 Undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 1968 December (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 1968 December (Cont'd.) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1968 November (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 1968 November (Cont'd.) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 1968 October (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 1968 October (Cont'd.) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - 1968 September (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 1968 September (Cont'd.) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1968 August (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1968 July (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1968 June (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1968 May (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 1968 April (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1968 March (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1968 February (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - 1968 January (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 1969 General (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 1969 Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1969 December (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 1969 November (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 1969 October (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 1969 September (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - 1969 August (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - 1969 August (Cont'd.) (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 1969 June (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 1969 May (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 1969 May (Cont'd.) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 1969 April (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 1969 March (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 1969 February (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 1969 January (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 1969 January (Cont'd.) (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 1970 General (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 1970 Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 1970 December (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 1970 November (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 1970 October (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 1970 September (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 1970 August (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 1970 July (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 1970 June (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - 1970 May (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - 1970 April (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - 1970 March (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - 1970 February (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 1970 January (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 1971 General (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 1971 Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1971 December (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1971 November (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 1971 October (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 1971 September (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 1971 August (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - 1971 July (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - 1971 June (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - 1971 May (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - 1971 April (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - 1971 March (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 1971 January (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - 1972 General (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - 1972 Undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - 1972 December (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 1972 November (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 1972 October (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 1972 September (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 1972 August (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 1972 July (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 1972 June (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - 1972 May (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - 1972 April (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - 1972 March (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - 1972 February (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - 1972 January (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - 1973 General (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - 1973 Undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - 1973 December (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - 1973 November (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 1973 October (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 1973 September (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 1973 August (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 1973 July (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 1973 June (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 1973 May (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 1973 April (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 1973 March (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 1973 February (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 1973 January (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 1974 General (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 1974 Undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 1974 December (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 1974 November (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - 1974 October (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - 1974 September (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - 1974 August (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - 1974 July (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - 1974 June (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - 1974 May (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - 1974 April (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 1974 March (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - 1974 February (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 1974 January (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - 1975 General (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - 1975 Undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 1975 December (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - 1975 November (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - 1975 October (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - 1975 September (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 1975 August (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - 1975 July (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - 1975 June (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 1975 May (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - 1975 April (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 1975 March (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 1975 February (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 1975 January (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - 1975 General (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - 1976 Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - 1976 December (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 1976 November (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - 1976 October (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - 1976 September (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - 1976 September (Cont'd.) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - 1976 August (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - 1976 July (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - 1976 June (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 1976 May (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - 1976 April (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 1976 March (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - 1976 February (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - 1976 January (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - 1977 General (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - 1977 Undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - 1977 December (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - 1977 November (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 1977 November (Cont'd.) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - 1977 October (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 1977 October (Cont'd.) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - 1977 September (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - 1977 September (Cont'd.) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - 1977 August (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - 1977 July (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 1977 June (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 1977 May (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 1977 April (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 1977 March (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 1977 February (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 1977 January (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 1978 General (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1978 Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - 1978 December (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - 1978 November (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 1978 November (Cont'd.) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 1978 October (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - 1978 October (Cont'd.) (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - 1978 September (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 1978 September (Cont'd.) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 1978 August (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 1978 August (Cont'd.) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - 1978 July (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 1978 July (Cont'd.) (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - 1978 June (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - 1978 May (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 1978 May (Cont'd.) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 1978 April (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 1978 April (Cont'd.) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 1978 March (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 1978 March (Cont'd.) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 1978 February (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 1978 February (Cont'd.) (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 1978 January (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 1978 January (Cont'd.) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 1979 General (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 1979 Undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 1979 December (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 1979 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 1979 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 1979 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - 1979 November (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 1979 November (Cont'd. ) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 1979 October (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 1979 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 1979 October (Cont'd. 2 ) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 1979 September (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 1979 September (Cont'd. ) (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 1979 August (Box 45, Folder 1)